[{"answer": "Well, one of the big things has come out, you mentioned Chris Christie earlier is that someone in the Romney Campaign apparently turned over their vice- presidential vetting file to the authors Mark Halperin and John Heilemann.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "What are the juiciest tidbits you have in from the last few hours?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "I mean I presume Newt will now try and say the nice things to Governor Christie quite hard when you read that about yourself, isn't it?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "It's pretty much in the bag with the two big races as they are every off of year or the New Jersey Governor's race and the Virginia race.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Any surprises in store or is it pretty much in the bag you think?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "It was a tough campaign.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "ORGAN: Has he gone fat to Chris Christie to say sorry or explain himself?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, as you know, because we've talked about it before, I think governors have an advantage in running for the nomination in 2016.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Do you need somebody that can raise for the White House who has that ability?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Look.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Is there any doubt, Newt, to think that she's going to run -- Hillary Clinton?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "And how do you fix it?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "He is a guy that needs to know his place with you.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Is he deeply unpleasant as everyone tries to say he is?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "I would go with Martin.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "If you were going into battle tomorrow again say the New York Giants and you could choose either Richie Incognito or Jonathan Martin to be alongside you, who would you go for?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Well, I think Glenn Greenwald has been very much more -- far more eloquent than I could be about the issue.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Were would you draw the line?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I don't know enough about that, I didn't know that, but I was very disappoint when he said, you know, you could trust us and he implied that we will fix this thing and it's like, you know, that he is lying and on top of that, you asked earlier is he in control of it, I don't think that he is.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "What do you think of that, is that another example is letting you down on transparency?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I was in boarding school.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Do you remember it vividly, where were you when it happened?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, I -- from my point of view, when I was -- I didn't know what I knew then.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Is America a better or worst country now than it was in the '60s?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "When I was in the infantry, I saw men blown away.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "What makes you so convinced that Lee Harvey Oswald did not attack alone?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Well, you can keep saying that but, you know, people have dig in all the time, and there aren't always records.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Do we ever know which one (ph)?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Well, I like Roosevelt and Kennedy I would -- I did not experience Roosevelt.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "... more than once in your lifetime, who would you have?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Not that you have to you can be a great song writer and great singer but that's swagger, that extra swagger something that becomes more memorable and it adds to the stage performance, and as of that your presence is there and it adds to your, you know, your -- how people view you I think in the public side.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "To be a great rock legend, do you have to have a dash of fashion (inaudible) about you?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Well if I knew that, you know I think it's tough.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What is the solution to Detroit's problems you think?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I think we are.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "It's establish -- should more great Americans success stories be thinking more into stop out sourcing so much?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "You know first of all musically he shattered everything that was out there at the time when he came on all of the great artist whether it was the Beatles or Eric Clapton at the time of the who they were all afraid of Jimmy Hendrix because he was so powerful musically.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "ORGAN: Really, why him?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "131104pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Is there any chance?", "qSentId": 504}]